Divac online
it's me someone must be hacking I hope
we don't get banned for this
diva in the flesh Oh can I get your
autograph only if I could get yours too
I love your new album
Divac just tell me one thing where'd you
learn to shoot like that 16-bit hero
may I love reading your journal I'm so
jealous you get to go to all those
places that's true I guess you don't get
to travel very much
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
of course here you go love Deva
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
Oh after this match is over right now
it's time to get serious
the destruction caused by the ominous
kheer it reminds me of home things can
be destroyed but as long as the people
are strong they can always be rebuilt
isn't a game are you sure life isn't a
game soldier 76
I can't stand you hackers you give those
of us with still a bad name you know
that isn't the kind of hacking I do
right
any chance you'd let me peek under the
hood of your Mick
this is no place for children who are
you calling a child
this is no place for children hey I'm no
ankle biter
a giant gorilla just like in those old
video games I did that a lot
diva have you seen the swatter course no
that is what I call a Mac size isn't
everything
[Music]
I think your clocks off
it's a good thing I brought an umbrella
maybe next time
I think this pigs a little undercooked
no hats for you